ICICI LBAT General Insurance Company ICICI
GI has released its audited business results for the financial year 2024-25.   The
company has reported excellent performance and a
strong increase in profits and premium growth.  The company's
GDPI i.e. Gross Direct Premium
Income
stood at ₹6833 crore in FY25, which is 8.3% higher
than ₹4776 crore in FY24 last year.
This growth is
much better than the industry average of 6.2%.
If we exclude the new IRDA accounting norms, the
growth has been 11%.  Whereas the growth of the industry has been
recorded at 8.6%.  The company's
PBT, i.e., profit before tax,
increased by 30% to ₹321 crore in FY25.
Which was
₹255 crore in financial year 24.  If we look at the PAD i.e.
profit after tax, it has also increased by 30.7% to
reach ₹258 crore.  Which was
₹1919 crore in financial year 24.  PAT
saw a marginal decline of 1.9% in Quarter 4.   The
combined ratio of the company in FY25 is
102.8%.  Whereas in FY24 it was
103.3%.  Excluding CAT, it
stood at 102.4% and 102.5%, which
reflects better discipline in underwriting.  The
Board of Directors of the Company has proposed a
final dividend of Rs 7 per share for the financial year 25.  According to
this, the
total dividend for the entire year will be ₹12.50
i.e. ₹12.5 per share.  Apart from this, the
company's return on average equity
stood at 19.1% in FY25, which was
17.2% in FY24.
Apart from this, the company's solvency ratio
stood at 2.69 times, which is
much higher than the regulatory minimum requirement of 1.5 times.  So
yesterday on 15th April 2025 after market hours
ICICI GI announced its FY25
results and
also offered a dividend of ₹7 to investors.